<content>
	<item id="1">
		<quote>I keep one eye on the stars, so I know what to aim for.</quote>
		<who>General Quintus Tiberius (105-135)</who>
		<more>Died falling off the Alpine Pass when distracted by a meteor shower</more>
	</item>
	<item id="2">
		<quote>Wise men try everything once.  Fear is no excuse for ignorance.</quote>
		<who>Xi Tai Lao (803-844)</who>
		<more>Died discovering gunpowder</more>
	</item>
	<item id="3">
		<quote>Remember the little things.  A brilliant sunrise fills me like no bread ever could.</quote>
		<who>Saint Lucia of Carvanne (942-964)</who>
		<more>Starved to death</more>
	</item>
	<item id="4">
		<quote>When life turns dark, trust in your fellow man; they alone hold the keys to peace and enlightenment.</quote>
		<who>Father Pedro diCampagna (1402-1441)</who>
		<more>Burned at the stake for heresy</more>
	</item>
	<item id="5">
		<quote>Smart men plan for the worst.  Great men turn the worst around.</quote>
		<who>General Maxime de Tièmes (1774-1805)</who>
		<more>Died when his army was decimated at the Battle of Deschamps</more>
	</item>
	<item id="6">
		<quote>Winners move first.  Losers get leftovers.  The rest are just cattle.</quote>
		<who>Lieutenant Mark Vardy (1838-1862)</who>
		<more>Died in a failed ambush when he forgot to equip his troops with ammunition</more>
	</item>
	<item id="7">
		<quote>There is nothing in this world so awesome as a man exercising his knowledge.  Immortality follows genius.</quote>
		<who>Winston Albertson (1890-1921)</who>
		<more>Died of electrocution after bringing a light bulb into the bath to read</more>
	</item>
	<item id="8">
		<quote>If I stayed down like they told me, I'd never have been able to beat the odds.</quote>
		<who>Marcus Rayburn (1902-1928)</who>
		<more>Died of a brain aneurysm during a boxing match</more>
	</item>
	<item id="9">
		<quote>Death holds no sway over a man who can put one foot in front of the other, and knows where he's going.</quote>
		<who>Louis Tank Williams (1917-1945)</who>
		<more>Died falling off the gangplank upon arriving home from World War II</more>
	</item>
	<item id="10">
		<quote>Everyone has the potential to change the world, if they can see past the fads and focus on that which is truly great.</quote>
		<who>Wilbur Axelrod (1951-1997)</who>
		<more>Died in poverty when his Laserdisc manufacturing company collapsed</more>
	</item>
	<item id="11">
		<quote>I find the will to succeed in the words and actions of the great thinkers of history.  With their guidance, I am unstoppable.</quote>
		<who>Jamila Allidina (1979-2009)</who>
		<more>Crushed to death when a library bookcase collapsed on her</more>
	</item>
	<item id="12">
		<quote>You can beat any odds if you try.  The only thing holding you back is caution.</quote>
		<who>Brian Spaeth (1975-2008)</who>
		<more>Exploded while filming motorcycle vs. helicopter climax to Prelude to a Super Airplane (2009, directed by Michael Bay)</more>
	</item>
	<item id="13">
		<quote>Fear is the body's way of protecting itself from the unknown.  Beat that, and nothing in this world can stop you.</quote>
		<who>Piper Hawking (1835-1864)</who>
		<more>Eaten while trying to domesticate lions in Africa</more>
	</item>
</content>